baumundpferdgarten.com 2016-12-04

# Privacy Policy

Baum und Pferdgarten A/S and/or any of its associated companies take its relationship with all our users seriously, and this includes how we handle the data you give us. Baum und Pferdgarten A/S is committed to meeting the requirements of all relevant laws and codes. This Privacy Policy sets out the ways Baum und Pferdgarten A/S processes any personal data collected via its Online Store. 

**1\. WHEN DO WE COLLECT PERSONAL INFORMATION?**

Our Online Store is free for you to browse through and read. We only ask for your email address for the following reasons;

  * \- If you want to purchase product(s) from the Online Store
  * \- If you want to contact us, send us an email or offer feedback
  * \- If you want to receive Baum und Pferdgarten A/S news and exclusive offers via email

We only collect personal information (such as your name and address details) if you choose to provide that information to us in response to our request.

**2\. WHAT DO WE DO WITH THE INFORMATION?**

We will require you to provide particular personal information such as your credit card details and your billing address for the purposes of completing your order. We will only use this information for the purposes of managing your order or your usage of the Online Store.

Providing additional personal information is up to you. We collect personal information to e-mail you with updates, news and special offers, to respond to your questions or comments, to register you for certain features on the  Online Store. 

**3\. ASKING YOUR PERMISSION**

 We will not send you email updates unless you have accepted to receive our newsletter.

**4\. HOW TO UNSUBSCRIBE**

We always provide you with the opportunity to opt in or out of receiving communication via email.

Baum und Pferdgarten A/S’s policy is to allow users to unsubscribe from our regular emails at any time. You can do this by clicking on the Unsubscribe link at the bottom of the email you've received. Can you also unsubscribe by clicking on the "-" sign under Newsletter Sign-up box - this will give you the option to Unsubscribe. Alternatively you can email us [custo](mailto:costumerservice@bruunsbazaar.com)[merservice@baumundpferdgarten.com](mailto:merservice@baumundpferdgarten.com) , select Newsletter as Subject line and write the word “Unsubscribe” in the subject line.

If you have sent a message asking us to stop sending emails, and this hasn’t happened, it may be because the email address to which we are sending them is not the same as the address you sent your request from. Please check the address we are using and include this information in your request. The easiest way to do this is to return to us the whole of the unwanted email. The address we are sending to is included at the bottom of the message.

**5\. WHO PROCESSES YOUR INFORMATION?**

Baum und Pferdgarten A/S (and those people or companies employed by Baum und Pferdgarten A/S who help make this Online Store, its content and its services) will process and use the information you tell us in order to respond to your feedback - like responding to problems, improving our services and gearing what we do to suit your requirements further.  

Beyond this, we will not share your information with any other company without your consent unless we are required to do so by law, if you have won a prize or if you have made a request for specific information. If you give us consent when you register with Baum und Pferdgarten A/S, then we may share your information with other companies in order that they can contact you with information, promotions, products, services and offers that may be interesting to you.  

We will never sell your information to any other company. 

**6\. USE OF COOKIES  **

Baum und Pferdgarten A/S uses cookies in order to provide a better service or identify which pages on the Online Store are of special interest and to analyze online statistics. A cookie is a small piece of information which an online store stores via your web browser on your computer and which can later be retrieved. Cookies cannot be read by an online store other than the one that set it. Most cookies last only through one session or visit to our Online Store. 

You are free to decline the use of cookies. Most web browsers permit to block or delete cookies. If you do not wish to use cookies when visiting our online store it can affect your shopping experience, since we among other things use cookies to update your shopping basket. If you want to make a purchase the use of cookies is mandatory since it otherwise not will be possible to place an order.

We use services from Google (Google Analytics) to collect web statistics. Cookies from this provider among other things allow us to see which pages are visited, where the traffic comes from etc. We use the information to improve the user experience on our website and to analyze on sales.

**7\. WHAT DO WE DO TO SAFEGUARD PERSONAL INFORMATION?**

We have instituted safeguards to check that our internal procedures meet our high policy standards. We also use our best efforts to be sure that third parties who work with us as our agents to make this Online Store and its contents available to you and to fulfill your orders and requests, agree to protect personal information that they must access in order to serve our Online Store and our visitors. We limit access to personal information about you to employees who we believe reasonably need to come into contact with that information to provide products or services to you or in order to do their jobs. 

**8\. CHANGES TO OUR PRIVACY POLICY  **

Any changes to the Privacy Policy will be posted here. 

If Baum und Pferdgarten A/S wishes to make material changes to the way we use your personal information we will ask for your consent before we do so. 

**9\. ANYTHING ELSE I SHOULD KNOW?   **

Except as otherwise provided, Baum und Pferdgarten A/S will NOT disclose any information processed by us to any third party, unless required to do so by law. 

© Baum und Pferdgarten A/S 2014. All Rights Reserved.
